Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
David A. Clarke papers
1974-1997
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Clarke, David A.
MS2010
211 Linear Feet
David A. Clarke (1943-1997) served as the Ward One Representative on the Council of the District of Columbia from 1975 to 1982, and served as Chairman of the Council between 1983 and 1991. In 1993, he was elected to complete the term of the late John A. Wilson, and in 1995 he was reinstated to serve another four-year term, where he served until his death in 1997. This collection contains correspondence, subject files, campaign and election records, clippings, legal documents, photographs, and artifacts. Materials date from 1974 to 1997.
Arrangement note
This collection is arranged in two series according to when the papers were received. Part 1 of the collection was received in 1990, and Part 2 was received after Clarke's death in 1997.
Biographical/Historical note
David A. Clarke (1943-1997) served as the Ward One Representative on the Council of the District of Columbia from 1975 to 1982, and served as Chairman of the Council between 1983 and 1991. In 1993, he was elected to complete the term of the late John A. Wilson, and in 1995 he was reinstated to serve another four-year term, where he served until his death in 1997.
Clarke was a member of the National Board of Directors of the Southern Christian Leadership Conference and the NAACP Legal Defense Fund-Washington Committee. He grew up in the Skyland and Shaw areas of Washington, D.C. and attended public schools in the District. He received a B.A. in religion from George Washington University and a J.D. from Howard University School of Law.
The David A. Clarke School of Law at the University of the District of Columbia was named for Clarke in 1998.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of the Honorable David A. Clarke, Chairman of the Council of the District of Columbia, 1990 [1991.002]. Additional accessions were received from the estate of David A. Clarke in 1997 and 2000.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, subject files, campaign and election records, clippings, legal documents, photographs, audio and video recordings, and artifacts. Materials in subject files pertain to D.C. legislation, organizations, neighborhoods, businesses, and individuals. Correspondence includes letters from constituents as well as legislative drafts and proposals, reports of the Council, memoranda, articles, and invitations to events. Materials date from 1974 to 1997.
These papers were received in two separate donations, one in 1990 and the second after Clarke's death in 1997. These accessions became two separate series. Before ordering a box, please note the series to which it belongs.
Washington (D.C.) Politics and government; City council members -- Washington (D.C.); District of Columbia. City Council.; George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae
- Part 1 (donated 1990), 1976-1990; Series 1; 82 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains reports, correspondence, clippings, proposals, and legislation, all arranged by subject or proper name. The material dates from 1976-1990, and was donated in 1990.
  - Subject files, 1976-1990; Series 1 Subseries 1
    - Abbot, Carolyn, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abrams and Associates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abramson Associates, Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Abramson Civic Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Abscot Place, N.E., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Abuse-Police Survey, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Academic Interaction, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - ACORN (Association for Community Organization for Reform Now), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - ACRT, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Action Group Washington Area Waterfront, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Active Christians Today Political Action Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - ACT UP/DC, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Acupuncture, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Adams (J.Q.) Community School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 2611 Adams Mill Road, N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 2630 Adams Mill Road,Displacement of Tenants, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 2630 Adams Mill Road-"Renovation", undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 2627-2633 Adams Mill Road, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 2900 Adams Mill Road Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Adams Morgan Community Development Corp., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Adams Morgan Community Food Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Adams Morgan Day, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Adams Morgan Family Medical Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Adams Morgan Neighborhood Celebration Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Adams Morgan Organization (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Adams Morgan Organization (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - ADASA (Alcohol and Drug Abuse Services Administration), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ADD Arts (Activities for Downtown Development the Arts), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Adelante, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Adero House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - AD HOC Committee to stop Shelter, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Neighborhood Commissions, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Arthur A. Adler, Clothier, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ASO (Adoptees Search Organization), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Committee on Washington Airports, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - AESME Council 20, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Aetna Life and Casualty, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - AFDC (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - AFDC (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - AFDC (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - AFGE (American Federation of Government Employees), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - AFGE Local 1733,President James E. Hooks, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - AFL-CIO, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - African American Coalition, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - African Art Museum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - African/Asian Development Bank (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - African/Asian Development Bank (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - African Drummers and Dancers,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - African Heritage Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - African Methodist Episcopal Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - African National Congress, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Africare, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Afro-American Bicentennial Corp., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Afro-American Datanamics,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Afro-American Heritage Museum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - AFSCME,D.C. Council 20, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Ahmadiya Muslim Community, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - John Akridge Co., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - AIDS, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - AIDS walk, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Alabama Avenue Renaissance Plan, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Albemarle Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Albright Memorial United Methodist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Alcohol Advisory Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Alcohol/Drug Abuse Developmental Services (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Alcohol/Drug Abuse Developmental Services (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Alderson,WVA Women's Correctional Facilities (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Alderson,WVA Women's Correctional Facilities (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Alexander Shepard School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - All Saints Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - All Souls Church,Unitarian, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Allergy and Asthma Hospital of America, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Alley Library, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Alliance of Taxicab businessmen of Washington,D.C., Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Allison St.,N.W. 1400 block, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Alpha Pi Chi, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Alpha Wives of Washington,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Alternative Schools Parents Consortium, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Alzheimer's disease and Related Disorders Association,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Alzheimer's Disease Research, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Alzheimer's Family Relief Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Ambassador Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Ambulance Service, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - American Association for Retired Persons, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - American Bar Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - American Board of Examiners in Crisis Intervention, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - American Bridge Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - American Cancer Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - American Capital Life Insurance Co., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - American Civil Liberties Union of National Capital Area, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - American Committee of Africa, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - American Contract Compliance Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - American Council of Life Insurance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - American Council on Taiwan, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Americans for Democratic Action-Greater WashingtonChapter, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - American Diabetes Association of Washington,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - American Federation of Government, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - American Federation of Teachers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - American Film Institute, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - American Foundation for Law and Government,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - American Friends Service Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - American Heart Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - American Hotel and Motel Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - American Institute of Architects, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - American Jewish Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - American Jewish Congress, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - American Lung Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - American Medical Management Public Hospital Division, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - American Muslim Mission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - American Personnel and Guidance Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - American Planning Association National Capital Area Chapter, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - American Red Cross, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - American Resort and Residential Development Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - American Security Bank, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - American University, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - American University Citizens Park Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - American Veterans of WWII,Korea-Vietnam, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - American War Mothers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - American Youth Work Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - AMSAT Communications, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - AMTRACK, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Anacostia Carry out (Good Hope Carry out), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Anacostia Community Day, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Anacostia Congress Heights Red Cross Service Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Anacostia Economic Development Corp. (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Anacostia Economic Development Corp. (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Anacostia Museum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Anacostia Recycling Action Project / RAP, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Anacostia River, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Anacostia Senior High School Gospel Choir, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Anchor Mental Health Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Ancient Egyptian Arabic Order Nobles Mystic Shrine, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Andrew Cacho African Drummers and Dancers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Andromeda Hispano Mental Health Center (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Andromeda Hispano Mental Health Center (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Andromeda Hispano Mental Health Center (3 of 3) petition to save, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Annual Service to Youth Awards Luncheon, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Annual Christmas Party, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Antall, Joseph, Minister of the Republic of Hungary, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Anthony Bowen YMCA Building, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Anti-Defamation League, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Antioch Law School (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Antioch Law School (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Antioch Law School (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Antioch Law School (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Anti-Rape Week, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Apartment Improvement Program,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Apartment and Office Building Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Request Forms Tenant Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Appreciation Breakfast, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - David Apter and Associates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - ARCH (Action to Rehabilitate Community Housing), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Arboretum Neighborhood Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Arboretum Young Adults Society of Washington,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Archdiocese of Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Area B Mental Health Care (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Area B Mental Health Care (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Arena Stage, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Armstrong High School Alumni Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Arnold and Porter, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Around the Corner to the World, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Arrington Youth Coalition and Community Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Art Against AIDS, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Art D.C. (D.C. Artworks), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Art Deco Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Art and Humanities Commission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Arthur Anderson and Co., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Article by David Clarke, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Artist Interaction, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Arts in the Academy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Artspace, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Asbestos, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Ascot Place Community Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ashley Condominiums,2038 18th Street, NW, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Asian Pacific Islander Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Asian TV News, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Associated Catholic Charities, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Associates for Renewal in Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Association for Community Based Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Association of D.C. Condominium Boards, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Association of Homeless Service Providers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Association of Plaintiffs Trial Attorneys, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Association for Retarded Citizens, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Association of School Psychologists, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The Atlantic Exchange,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Auditor,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Augustana Lutheran Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Austrian Embassy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Auto Insurance National Conference, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - ATT Communication, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Awards, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - AYUDA,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - AZT, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - B W Stat Laboratory, Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - BABES, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Back to Pentecost Crusade Ministers,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Background 7 and Correspondence News Releases, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - BAH'A'I's, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Bairstow Gallery House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Bail Agency, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Ballou PTSA, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Bancroft School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Bangkok Cultural Visit, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Banneker School Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Baptist Home for Children, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Baptist Ministers' Conference D.C. and Vicinity, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Barney Circle Freeway, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Barney Neighborhood House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Mayor Barry, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Bartender's Ball, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Bates Area Civic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Bates Street Block Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Battered Wives, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Beacon Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Bee Coalition Neighborhood Walk, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Beech-Reed Communications, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Behavior Effectuation Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Beiro Construction Company, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Beitzell and Co.,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Belgium,Ambassador of, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Belmont Rd.,N.W.,1400 Block, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Belmont Rd.,N.W.,2009 Block, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Belmont Rd.,N.W.,Tenants Cooperative, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ben Franklin 5 and 10 Store-2453 18th Street, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Benjamin Banneker Community Laboratory Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Benning Elementary School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Benning Heights Cooperative, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Benning-Ridge Civic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Berean Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - The Berkshire (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - The Berkshire (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Bethesda Capital Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Bethesda New Life Gospel Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Bethune Museum and Archives,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)